<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>The Huntington News &#187; Crime Log</title>
	<atom:link href="http://huntnewsnu.com/category/crime-log/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://huntnewsnu.com</link>
	<description>The independent student newspaper of the Northeastern community</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 18:38:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.0.3</generator>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log: Dec. 1 &#8211; 5, 2010</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/12/crime-log-dec-1-5-2010/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/12/crime-log-dec-1-5-2010/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 07:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=14103</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Entry of the Week: Dec. 4, 2:35 p.m. - Officers responded to a call reporting a loud party on the roof of 80 Fenway. When officers arrived, they found 250 people on the roof of the building, many of whom were wearing T-shirts advertising a keg party tour. NUPD officers learned of several other locations on the party tour and closed a building on Hemenway Street before the party could start. The three 20-year-old students who hosted the party were reported to OSCCR, and will be summonsed for providing alcohol to minors. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>by Todd Feather, News Correspondent</p>
<p>Wednesday, Dec. 1<br />
12:30 p.m.<br />
The manager of Wollaston’s in Marino Center reported he caught a student shoplifting $10 worth of beauty supplies. The student was banned from Wollaston’s and reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>3 p.m.<br />
A student reported she received a phone call from her former boyfriend, with whom she has an active restraining order against. He will be charged with violating the restraining order.</p>
<p>A student reported his bicycle was stolen from outside West Village A, where he locked it Nov. 25.</p>
<p>Thursday, Dec. 2<br />
2:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported she lost her wristlet purse, containing $3 and credit cards, as she was walking through the Ruggles T station. She believes it may have fallen while she was walking.</p>
<p>9 p.m.<br />
A student reported he left his wallet, containing $50, credit cards, and his license, in an unlocked locker in the Marino Center at 6 p.m. When he returned at 7:30 p.m., it was gone.</p>
<p>Friday, Dec. 3<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
A student reported his car, which was parked in a housing development near West Village since 9 p.m. the previous night, had a broken window. The student’s backpack, which contained textbooks, was missing.</p>
<p>2 a.m.<br />
Northeastern University Police Department (NUPD) officers responded to a call from White Hall about a drunk student yelling and banging on a dorm room door. When officers arrived they found an 18-year-old student who claimed to be locked out of her room. After officers questioned her, they discovered she had her room key in her pocket. She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11:45 a.m.<br />
A student reported her wallet was taken from InfoCommons, where she was studying the previous night. The wallet was later turned in to lost and found, but while attempting to determine the identity of the owner, officers discovered a fake ID. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported her bicycle was stolen from the courtyard outside Burstein Hall, where she had locked it at noon. Several hours later, the student contacted NUPD again to report she saw a man with her bicycle on Forsyth Street. When officers arrived, they interviewed Oscar Cearrion, 41, who admitted knowing the bicycle was stolen when he bought it for $20. Officers arrested Cearrion, who has a criminal record, for receiving stolen property. He gave officers some information about the seller, but only knew him by a nickname.</p>
<p>7:15 p.m.<br />
Three roommates in West Village A reported they were worried for their safety after arguments with their fourth roommate escalated. Two of the roommates chose to be relocated in different housing for the weekend, and officers escorted them back to their room to retrieve their belongings. The other student decided to stay in the room.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.<br />
An officer near Churchill Hall saw a middle-aged man arguing with a student. When the officer questioned the two, the student said the older man, David Williams, 47, gave him a check and asked him to deposit it in his ATM account, then withdraw the cash and give it to Williams. The officer looked up Williams&#8217; record and arrested him on two outstanding warrants, both for similar cases of larceny by false pretense.</p>
<p>Saturday, Dec. 4<br />
2 a.m.<br />
An officer saw a group of seemingly intoxicated students walking behind Curry Student Center. One member of the group, a 17-year-old who was visiting her 18-year-old friend, lost consciousness on a bench in Krentzman Quad. She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and the student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>A Resident Assistant (RA) in Speare Hall reported two drunk students vomiting in a bathroom. When officers arrived they found two 18-year-old students, who EMTs determined did not need medical attention. The students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p><strong>Entry of the Week</strong><br />
2:35 p.m.</p>
<p>Officers responded to a call reporting a loud party on the roof of 80 Fenway. When officers arrived, they found 250 people on the roof of the building, many of whom were wearing T-shirts advertising a keg party tour. NUPD officers learned of several other locations on the party tour and closed a building on Hemenway Street before the party could start. The three 20-year-old students who hosted the party were reported to OSCCR, and will be summonsed for providing alcohol to minors.<br />
11 p.m.<br />
An officer saw a 20-year-old Wentworth Institute of Technology student walking on Gainsborough Street with an open can of beer. The officer confiscated the beer and Wentworth authorities were notified.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.<br />
An officer in the Columbus Street parking lot saw a 20-year-old man, who was visiting a student, transfer 15 beers from a case to his backpack. The officer stopped the visitor, who eventually admitted to having the beer and turned it over to the officer.</p>
<p>11:45 p.m.<br />
A student called NUPD to report a friend of his was drunk near the Park Street T station. NUPD officers located the 18-year-old student in question, who was taken to Tufts Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Sunday, Dec. 5<br />
2 a.m.<br />
A student reported his 22-year-old visitor, who was drunk, fell and injured his nose in West Village A. The visitor was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center.</p>
<p>A 19-year-old student reported her wallet was stolen while she was at a party at 103 Hemenway St.</p>
<p>2:30 a.m.<br />
A student reported her friend, a 20-year-old student, was drunk in an apartment at 84 Gainsborough St. The friend was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>4:15 a.m.<br />
Six students reported their apartment was burglarized while they were at a party that night. The students told officers they had left several friends in their apartment when they left to go to the party, and their friends left the door unlocked. Four laptops, two televisions and two iPods were missing.</p>
<p>3:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported her iPod missing from an unlocked locker in the Cabot Center, where she accidentally left it after swimming the previous night.</p>
<p>A student reported two expensive turntable needles were taken from his backpack, which he left unattended briefly in the International Village food court. The backpack also contained an iPod, laptop and cell phone, which were not taken.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/12/crime-log-dec-1-5-2010/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log: Nov. 15 &#8211; 30, 2010</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/12/crime-log-73/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/12/crime-log-73/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 09:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Todd Feathers]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=13917</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Entry of the Week, Friday, Nov. 19,  2 a.m. : BPD officers reported they found an intoxicated 19-year-old student on Columbus Avenue wearing only shorts. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>by Todd Feathers, News Correspondent</p>
<p>Monday, Nov. 15</p>
<p>9 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported she lost her wallet, containing credit cards and $75, in the Ruggles T station.</p>
<p>2:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported two teenage boys grabbed her purse and ran off while she was loading her car on Coventry Street. The student chased after the two boys, who dropped her purse without taking anything.</p>
<p>5 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported a teenage boy approached him and demanded his valuables while he was walking on Coventry Street two hours earlier. The student shoved the suspect and ran away without anything being stolen.</p>
<p>5:40 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported a teenage boy unsuccessfully attempted to steal her purse while she was walking on Coventry Street three hours earlier. The Northeastern Division of Public Safety (NUPD) believes this incident may be related to similar attempted thefts on Coventry Street that day.</p>
<p>Tuesday, Nov. 16</p>
<p>10:15 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported his bicycle was stolen from the bike racks outside West Village G, where he had locked it with a cable lock Nov. 8.</p>
<p>Wednesday, Nov. 17</p>
<p>2 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported he parked and locked his bicycle outside International Village (INV) at 4 p.m. the previous day. When he returned at 8 a.m., he found the bike’s seat missing.</p>
<p>A student reported his cell phone was stolen from the Marino Center while he played basketball from 4:30 p.m. to 5 p.m. the previous day.</p>
<p>3:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported two teenage boys stole a package he was carrying while he was walking near Dewitt Drive.</p>
<p>10 p.m.</p>
<p>Two students reported their apartment at 58 Hemenway St. was broken into. Two laptops were missing, and officers discovered a window had been forced open. The BPD is conducting an investigation.</p>
<p>10 p.m.</p>
<p>Two students reported their bicycles were stolen from outside 650 Columbus Ave., where they had locked them together with a cable lock at 6 p.m.</p>
<p>Thursday, Nov. 18</p>
<p>4:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported her car window was broken and her backpack stolen from her car while it was parked in the Renaissance Parking Garage.</p>
<p>9:15 p.m.</p>
<p>A staff member reported her parking permit and GPS device were stolen from her unlocked car while it was parked in the Renaissance Parking Garage.</p>
<p>Friday, Nov. 19</p>
<p><strong>Entry of the Week:<br />
</strong>2 a.m.</p>
<p>BPD officers reported they found an intoxicated 19-year-old student on Columbus Avenue wearing only shorts. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>10 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported her bicycle frame was stolen from outside INV, where she had locked the front wheel of the bicycle at 8 p.m. the previous day.</p>
<p>11 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported her iPod was taken from the basement of INV, where she had left it at 11 a.m. the previous day.</p>
<p>Information Technology department staff members reported a wireless receiver was stolen from Snell Library earlier that day. NUPD officers are investigating.</p>
<p>12:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported his car window was broken and his iPod stolen from his car while it was parked on Huntington Avenue.</p>
<p>8 p.m.</p>
<p>A maintenance worker entered an apartment at 116 St. Stephen St. after Housing and Residential Life staff received a complaint of water leaking into the apartment below. The worker found a 20-year-old student intoxicated and unconscious on a couch. The student was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11 p.m.</p>
<p>NUPD officers responded to a student’s complaint about a loud party at 74 St. Stephen St. The officers broke the party up after finding empty alcohol containers and several underage students. The three 20-year-old students who hosted the party were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Saturday, Nov. 20</p>
<p>2 a.m.</p>
<p>NUPD officers responded to reports of a fight on St. Stephen Street, where they found two 21-year-old students who had been arguing. The fight was broken up and neither student pressed charges.</p>
<p>4:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student called NUPD to report her former boyfriend, a student, was banging on her apartment door. Officers contacted the boyfriend and told him to have no future contact with the student. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Monday, Nov. 22</p>
<p>7:30 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported her purse was stolen from Ell Hall while she was in a meeting. The purse was later found in a trash can with $40, several credit cards, and a camera missing.</p>
<p>Tuesday, Nov. 23</p>
<p>2 a.m.</p>
<p>An NUPD officer arrested Michael Kauffman, 22, and Jamayl Bohkari, 22, for assault and battery after he observed them assaulting another man on Forsyth Street. The victim told officers he had argued with Kauffman and Bohkari at the Our House East bar on Gainsborough Street earlier that night, and the two men had followed him when he left.</p>
<p>6:30 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported she had received several harassing phone calls from a stranger she allowed to borrow her phone two days earlier. NUPD officers traced the phone calls to a man with no connection to Northeastern and told him to stop contacting the student.</p>
<p>11:30 a.m.</p>
<p>A staff member reported her laptop was taken from a classroom in Hurtig Hall where she left it after a class.</p>
<p>12 p.m.</p>
<p>Two students reported a pair of jeans, a sweatshirt and several blouses were stolen from the laundry room in Smith Hall.</p>
<p>7:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A staff member in the INV administrative center reported receiving several harassing phone calls. NUPD officers are investigating the matter.</p>
<p>10:15 p.m.</p>
<p>A NUPD officer saw two students carrying a drunk 21-year-old student into INV. The student was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Saturday, Nov. 27</p>
<p>8:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported receiving dozens of unwanted calls and text messages from a former friend who is also a student. Officers ordered the student to cease all contact and he was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Monday, Nov. 29</p>
<p>1 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported her laptop was stolen from an apartment at 650 Columbus Ave., where she had spent the previous night. A cell phone belonging to the student who owned the apartment and the wallet of another visitor were also missing. The victims told officers another resident of the apartment had brought an unknown man into the apartment around 11 p.m. the previous night, and the door had been left unlocked afterward. NUPD officers are investigating the matter.</p>
<p>5:15 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported his bicycle was stolen from outside West Village G, where he left it locked Nov. 22.</p>
<p>5:45 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported his backpack, containing his laptop, was taken from a Dodge Hall classroom where he forgot it after a class.</p>
<p>Tuesday, November 30</p>
<p>3:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported her backpack, containing a laptop, calculator and textbook, was stolen from the back of her chair in the Marino Center between 2:30 p.m. and 3:15 p.m.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/12/crime-log-73/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log: Nov. 9 &#8211; 15, 2010</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-72/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-72/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 06:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=13667</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Entry of the Week: Monday, Nov. 15, 1 a.m. A woman from New York called NUPD to report her 15-year-old granddaughter had run away with her 18-year-old boyfriend, who is a Northeastern student. Officers found the granddaughter, who then spoke to her grandmother and agreed to take a bus back to New York. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By Todd Feathers, News Correspondent</p>
<p>Tuesday, Nov. 9</p>
<p>10:30 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported his cell phone was stolen from a Dodge Hall classroom, where he left it the previous day.</p>
<p>11 p.m.</p>
<p>A Resident Assistant (RA) in Kennedy Hall reported the smell of marijuana from a first floor suite. When officers arrived they found three 18-year-old students in the room and confiscated a pipe and less than an ounce of marijuana. The students were reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>Wednesday, Nov. 10</p>
<p>6 p.m.</p>
<p>As part of an ongoing drug investigation, an officer searched the room of an 18-year-old student in Speare Hall. The student turned over a marijuana grinder and a large knife. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>10 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported his wallet was stolen from InfoCommons, where he left it unattended for 10 minutes. When he canceled his credit cards, the student discovered several hundred dollars were already spent.</p>
<p>Thursday, Nov. 11</p>
<p>12:30 a.m.</p>
<p>A student reported he was punched for no apparent reason by an unknown college-aged man on Huntington Avenue.</p>
<p>10 p.m.</p>
<p>A student reported her cell phone stolen from the CyberCafe in International Village (INV), where she left it unattended for five minutes.</p>
<p>Friday, Nov. 12</p>
<p>11 a.m.</p>
<p>A student in the Massachusetts Avenue T station was punched in the back for no apparent reason by a middle-aged woman who then returned to her seat. The student left the station and reported the incident to the NUPD. The Massachusetts Bay Transit Authority (MBTA) Transit Police have taken over the investigation.</p>
<p>Noon</p>
<p>A student reported she left her iPad unattended in the food court at Ryder Hall for 10 minutes. Someone brought the iPad to lost-and-found and it was returned to the student.</p>
<p>4:30 p.m.</p>
<p>An officer patrolling the Fenway observed a 22-year-old man, who is unaffiliated with the university, smoking marijuana. The officer confiscated less than an ounce of marijuana and a pipe.</p>
<p>9 p.m.</p>
<p>A food service employee at the INV dining hall reported two men pouring beer into coffee cups under their table. Officers arrived and spoke to a 19-year-old student and his 19-year-old visitor, who admitted drinking beer. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>9:15 p.m.</p>
<p>While searching a 19-year-old student’s wallet brought in to lost-and-found, NUPD officers discovered a fake driver’s license. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>10:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A 19-year-old student in White Hall reported her 18-year-old boyfriend was vomiting. EMTs evaluated him, and he was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center. The student and her boyfriend admitted they were drinking in the room of another 19-year-old student, who was found to be heavily intoxicated. He was also taken to the hospital and was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A Resident Assistant reported two students, 18 and 19 years old, and their 19-year-old visitor were smoking marijuana in the West Village Quad. The two students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Saturday, Nov.13</p>
<p>12:45 a.m.</p>
<p>The Boston Police Department (BPD) requested the help of NUPD officers in shutting down a disruptive party at 216 Hemenway St. A 20-year-old student refused to leave the party and BPD officers arrested him for disorderly conduct and possession of methamphetamine and ecstasy. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2 a.m.</p>
<p>An RA in Speare Hall reported a drunk, 19-year-old student in the lobby. EMTs evaluated the student and determined he did not need medical attention. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.</p>
<p>An officer patrolling Hemenway Street saw a 20-year-old student drinking a beer. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A proctor at Davenport A reported a drunk 20-year-old student tried to enter the building without proper ID. An officer later found the student on Columbus Avenue. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Sunday, Nov. 14</p>
<p>2 a.m.</p>
<p>A student in Stetson West reported an 18-year-old student was drunk and needed assistance. Officers could not wake the student up, so she was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2 a.m.</p>
<p>An RA in INV reported a loud party and the sound of bottles clanking in a room. When officers arrived they found only one 18-year-old student in the room, with an empty beer can. In the room next door the officers found nine other students who had just entered through the bathroom. The 18-year-old student who hosted the party was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>3 a.m.</p>
<p>A student in Melvin Hall reported an 18-year-old student was drunk and needed assistance. EMTs evaluated the student and determined she did not need medical attention. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>8 a.m.</p>
<p>A proctor in INV reported a drunk 18-year-old student tried to enter the building without proper identification. Officers found the student asleep on a couch in the lobby. The student did not remember anything about the night before and could not find his wallet or cell phone. Officers helped him to his room, where he later found his wallet and cell phone. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>3 p.m.</p>
<p>Officers responded to a report of a student’s 17-year-old visitor locking himself in a Loftman Hall bathroom. When officers arrived the visitor had left, but he was later found in the Starbucks on Huntington Avenue. The visitor had run away from his home in Maine, and was picked up by his father at 8:30 p.m.</p>
<p>7:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student in 335 Huntington Ave. reported the door of another apartment in the building had been kicked in. The student who lives in the apartment had not reported the incident, but she told officers she had been out of the apartment from 7 a.m. to 7 p.m., and a laptop and some jewelry had been taken. The BPD has taken over the investigation.</p>
<p><strong>Entry of the Week: </strong>Monday, Nov. 15</p>
<p>1 a.m.</p>
<p>A woman from New York called NUPD to report her 15-year-old granddaughter had run away with her 18-year-old boyfriend, who is a Northeastern student. Officers found the granddaughter, who then spoke to her grandmother and agreed to take a bus back to New York.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-72/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log: Nov. 1 &#8211; 8, 2010</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-71/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-71/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 05:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=13497</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Wednesday, Nov. 6, 3 p.m. A student reported his cell phone was stolen in mid-September. The student told his parents of the theft, but they failed to cancel the service plan. He notified NUPD after his parents received a $7,000 phone bill.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By Todd Feathers, News Correspondent</p>
<p>Monday, Nov. 1<br />
3 p.m.<br />
A student reported her cell phone was stolen from an International Village (INV) bathroom. She later discovered she left the device in one of her classrooms, and her professor turned it in to the lost and found.</p>
<p>3:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported her purse was stolen during an Oct. 30 party at a Douglass Park apartment.</p>
<p>4:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported her cell phone and wallet, containing $35, fell out of her backpack Oct. 30 near Speare Commons.</p>
<p>10 p.m.<br />
While searching a 20-year-old student’s purse brought in to lost-and-found, Northeastern University Division of Public Safety (NUPD) officers found an ID belonging to the student’s 21-year-old sister. The student was reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>Tuesday, Nov. 2<br />
3:30 p.m.<br />
A staff member in Ryder Hall reported two digital cameras missing from an unlocked office while the staff members were out at lunch.</p>
<p>7:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported his laptop was stolen from a corridor in the Egan Research Center where he left it unattended from 5 p.m. to 7 p.m.</p>
<p>Wednesday, Nov. 3<br />
9:30 a.m.<br />
A staff member reported his parking permit was stolen from his unlocked car in the Gainsborough Parking Garage between 6 a.m. and 9:30 p.m.</p>
<p>3 p.m.<br />
A student reported his cell phone was stolen in mid-September. The student told his parents of the theft, but they failed to cancel the service plan. He notified NUPD after his parents received a $7,000 phone bill.</p>
<p>5 p.m.<br />
A Resident Assistant (RA) in the YMCA building reported finding marijuana and a pipe in a student’s room during health and safety inspections. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>6:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported his cell phone stolen from Dodge Hall, where he left it unattended for 15 minutes.</p>
<p>8 p.m.<br />
A student reported her ex-boyfriend, who is not a student, physically assaulted her. The police in the town where her ex-boyfriend lives have assumed jurisdiction, and he has been banned from campus.</p>
<p>Friday, Nov. 5<br />
12 p.m.<br />
A student reported she lost her cell phone between Ryder Hall and the Curry Student Center.</p>
<p>5:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported two teenage girls knocked her to the ground, kicked her and attempted to steal her purse in the alley between Smith and Melvin Halls. Students who witnessed the attempted robbery scared the teenagers off and nothing was taken.</p>
<p>Saturday, Nov. 6<br />
2:30 a.m.<br />
An RA in Stetson West reported an intoxicated 18-year-old student vomiting in a bathroom. EMTs evaluated the student and determined he did not need medical attention. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2:30 a.m.<br />
An NUPD officer saw a seemingly intoxicated man, who is not affiliated with the university, arguing with a group of people on Columbus Avenue. The officer restrained the man, who admitted he was trying to start a fight.</p>
<p>1:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported his backpack, which contained a laptop and an iPod, was stolen from near his chair in Qdoba at 393 Huntington Ave. while he ate.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.<br />
A student called NUPD to report he was concerned about his 23-year-old friend who was drunk and belligerent. NUPD officers responded and found the drunk student standing in traffic on Huntington Avenue. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center, reported to OSCCR and has apologized to the officers involved.</p>
<p>Sunday, Nov. 7<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
A RA found an 18-year-old student vomiting in INV. The student was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1 a.m.<br />
NUPD officers responded to a report of a disruptive party at 610 Columbus Ave. The party was broken up and the 23-year-old student who hosted the party was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:45 a.m.<br />
An RA in Davenport Commons A found a 19-year-old student unconscious in a hallway. The student was revived by EMTs, taken to Tufts Medical Center, and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported her laundry, including expensive designer clothing, was stolen from a dryer in Kennedy Hall, where she left it from 10 p.m. Nov. 3 to 1:30 p.m.</p>
<p>Monday, Nov. 8<br />
3:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported his bicycle, which was secured with a cable lock, was stolen from Centennial Common between 1:30 p.m. and 3:15 p.m.</p>
<p>4 p.m.<br />
A student reported his bicycle, which was secured with a cable lock, was stolen from a fence in front of Douglas Park between 1 p.m. and 3:30 p.m.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-71/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-70/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-70/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 07:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Jamieson]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=12899</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Friday, Oct. 29, 2 a.m. Police responded to reports of an assault on Huntington Avenue. A 21-year-old with no affiliation to the university stole a hat from a female student, who was walking with a friend. When her friend tried to stand up for her, the person who stole the hat punched the friend in the face. The student was not seriously injured. Boston Police Department (BPD) officers assumed jurisdiction over this case.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>by John Jamieson, News Correspondent</p>
<p>Tuesday, Oct. 26<br />
10 a.m.<br />
The manager of the Wollaston’s in West Village called to report that a man in his thirties shoplifted bottles of hand soap. The man fled with the soap before Northeastern University Division of Pubic Safety (NUPD) officers arrived.</p>
<p>4 p.m.<br />
A student called to report his laptop missing. He left it unattended in a common room on the second floor of Ell Hall for about 30 minutes, and when he returned, it was gone.</p>
<p>11:15 p.m.<br />
A student reported her iPod missing after she’d left her pocket book unattended in the Library Quad from 9 p.m. to 10:30 p.m.</p>
<p>Wednesday, Oct. 27<br />
1:30 p.m.<br />
A Resident Assistant (RA) doing a safety check on the seventh floor of West Village E called to report finding a smoke detector with a plastic bag over it in a room. The resident, 21, was found responsible for the violation and reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>3 p.m.<br />
A student reported she was concerned about how her former boyfriend, who has no affiliation with the university, was taking their break-up. NUPD officers assisted her in obtaining a domestic abuse restraining order against him.</p>
<p>9:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported she left her laptop unattended on the third floor of Kariotis Hall. When she returned an hour later, it was missing.</p>
<p>A student reported he left his laptop and chemistry book unattended on the fourth floor of Snell Library for about five minutes. When he came back, they were both gone.</p>
<p>11 p.m.<br />
A student reported a group of teenagers near the Park Street Massachusetts Bay Transit Authority (MBTA) Station stole her iPod. Transit Police later spotted a group of suspects near the Massachusetts Avenue Station and contacted NUPD to bring the victim there to see the group. The student identified members of the group, but said the one who actually took her iPod was not present. Transit Police officers will continue to investigate this case.</p>
<p>Thursday, Oct. 28<br />
4:45 p.m.<br />
A student left his iPhone unattended while he was at InfoCommons in Snell Library. He was at a printer for about 10 minutes, and returned to find it missing.</p>
<p>7:30 p.m.<br />
An NUPD detective visited an 18-year-old student in Stetson West as part of an ongoing drug investigation. During the meeting, the officer confiscated a vaporizer, bong, several blunts and less than an ounce of marijuana. The student was reported to OSCCR for the second time in a week.</p>
<p>8 p.m.<br />
An NUPD detective visited another 18-year-old student in Stetson West as part of an ongoing drug investigation. The officer confiscated a bong from the student, who admitted to smoking marijuana with the student mentioned in the previous entry. The second student was also reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>8:15 p.m.<br />
Two students reported seeing a man walking around campus with a backpack offering to sell students alcohol, or buy it for them. NUPD found the man, a 23-year-old with no affiliation to the university, and discovered that he did have alcohol in the backpack, although he claimed he wasn’t trying to sell it. The man was issued a trespassing ban and escorted off campus.</p>
<p>10 p.m.<br />
A student told an officer outside International Village (INV) that three men approached him and offered to sell him drugs. Officers investigated, found the men and questioned them. All three were arrested and their hallucinogenic mushrooms were confiscated. Jonathan Sullivan, 31, of Boston, was charged with trespassing and conspiracy to violate the controlled substance policy. Mark Donaldson, 23, who is reportedly homeless, was charged with trespassing, conspiracy to violate the controlled substance policy, and possession with intent to distribute. Daniel Kilroy, 27, of Dorchester, was charged with trespassing, conspiracy to violate the controlled substance policy, assault and battery on a police officer and intimidating a witness. Police said the last charge was because Kilroy threatened to kill the officer when he gets out of jail. All three men had previous police records.</p>
<p>10:30 p.m.<br />
A proctor in Loftman Hall reported an intoxicated 20-year-old student entered the building. NUPD officers found her unsteady on her feet and covered in vomit. She was uncooperative and gave officers a false name. She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center by ambulance. An 18-year-old student wanted to go in the ambulance with her, claiming to be her friend and sorority sister, but would not provide officers with the 20-year-old’s real name. This student was also intoxicated, but not enough to require hospitalization, so she was taken home by a friend. Both students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Friday, Oct. 29</p>
<p>2 a.m.<br />
<strong>Entry of the Week: </strong>Police responded to reports of an assault on Huntington Avenue. A 21-year-old with no affiliation to the university stole a hat from a female student, who was walking with a friend. When her friend tried to stand up for her, the person who stole the hat punched the friend in the face. The student was not seriously injured. Boston Police Department (BPD) officers assumed jurisdiction over this case.</p>
<p>3 a.m.<br />
A proctor in West Village C reported an intoxicated person trying to sneak in without proper identification. NUPD responded and found a 21-year-old student who lives off campus. When asked for identification, the student produced two different IDs: one with his name, and a Husky ID that belonged to someone else. The student said he was drinking off campus with friends, but got separated from them, and that it was too late to catch the train home. He was trying to find a student to put him up for the night, but could not remember the name of the student he was with. He said another student, who lived in a different residence hall, gave him the Husky Card. The intoxicated student was becoming disorderly, and officers told him he couldn’t stay and should call his parents. The student sat down and refused to leave or call his parents. Mark Chirokas, 21, was arrested for disorderly conduct. The next day, NUPD officers contacted the student to whom the NU ID belonged. The student was vague, and while he didn’t say the ID was stolen, he didn’t say that he gave Chirokas the ID.<br />
1:30 p.m.<br />
The manager of the Wollaston’s at the Marino Center reported a student stole eyedrops from the store. NUPD caught the student, who was banned from both Wollaston’s stores on campus and reported to OSCCR. The eyedrops were recovered and returned to the store.</p>
<p>8:15 p.m.<br />
A student reported she parked and locked her bicycle near the entrance of West Village A from around 3:30 p.m. to 4:30 p.m. She returned to find the bike stolen, along with the chain and cable lock.</p>
<p>9:30 p.m.<br />
NUPD officers heard over the BPD radio that a robbery occurred on Park Drive in the Back Bay Fens. The call included a description of the suspects. A group of people matching these descriptions, seen later on Forsyth Street, were detained. The two victims of the robbery identified three of the four suspects. BPD will continue to work on the case with those suspects, ages 16, 18 and 19. The items stolen have not been recovered, which included wallets and cell phones.</p>
<p>11:45 p.m.<br />
An RA in Davenport A reported seeing an intoxicated 19-year-old student. When NUPD found the student, she vomited. The officers assessed her condition and determined she was well enough to stay with her roommates for the night. She was reported to OSCCR</p>
<p>Saturday, Oct. 30<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
An RA reported an intoxicated 18-year-old student in Stetson West. An Emergency Medical Technician (EMT) evaluated his condition and allowed him to stay there for the night. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2 a.m.<br />
An anonymous caller reported an intoxicated 21-year-old student at Our House East on Gainsborough Street. An officer evaluated her and called an ambulance. She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2:15 a.m.<br />
An RA in Speare Hall reported a resident punched holes in the walls, shattered glass in the common room and broke a water fountain. NUPD found the resident intoxicated and disorderly. Nahba Bropleh, 18, was arrested for malicious destruction. He wouldn’t say why he did it, and was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2 p.m.<br />
A 21-year-old student reported his iPod stolen from his West Village B apartment. He said it was most likely taken around 2 a.m. or 3 a.m., when he was in his bedroom and his roommates propped the front door of the apartment open.</p>
<p>A student was sitting  on the curb near the Columbus Parking Garage and talking on his cell phone, when two teenagers approached him, demanded his cell phone and pulled out a knife. The student got up and ran down Columbus Avenue, while his assailants walked away in the other direction. By the time NUPD arrived, the suspects had left the area.</p>
<p>Sunday, Oct. 31<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
An RA reported an 18-year-old student vomiting in a bathroom on the third floor of Stetson West. The student said she had been drinking vodka and Four Loko at a party at Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT). She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center by ambulance and was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>12:45 a.m.<br />
A student reported losing her cell phone after playing hide-and-go-seek around campus with her friends. After an hour, she realized her phone was missing.</p>
<p>1:45 a.m.<br />
An intoxicated 18-year-old student was on a bench in the lobby of West Village H. She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center by ambulance and was reported to OSCCR. She would not answer any questions about where she had been or what she’d been drinking.</p>
<p>An RA reported an intoxicated student on the second floor of Stetson West. EMTs evaluated her condition and determined she was well enough to remain at home with her roommates. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2 a.m.<br />
An RA reported seeing an intoxicated student swipe into Willis Hall. EMTs determined the student was intoxicated, but not enough to require hospitalization. She said she’d been drinking Four Loko. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/11/crime-log-70/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-69/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-69/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 08:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=12812</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Friday, Oct. 22, 2 a.m. Officers responded to a call from the Renaissance Parking Garage about a student who appeared to be assaulted. Upon arrival, the officers found a drunk 19-year-old student in one of the stairwells. NUPD officers are uncertain how the student became injured. He was reported to OSCCR.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tuesday, Oct. 19<br />
8 a.m.<br />
A student reported that her planner, containing personal information, was missing from the Curry Student Center where she left it unattended.</p>
<p>Noon<br />
The Student Financial Services office contacted the Northeastern University Division of Public Safety (NUPD) to inform officers of payments made by a stolen credit card on a students account. NUPD is investigating.</p>
<p>Wednesday, Oct. 20<br />
9 p.m.<br />
Officers responded to a call reporting the smell of marijuana at 122 St. Stephen St. The officers found three students smoking and confiscated an undisclosed amount of marijuana from their room. All three students have been reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>Thursday, Oct. 21<br />
1 a.m.<br />
An NUPD officer on Massachusetts Avenue saw a man exit a car and threaten two students in another car with a baseball bat. Boston Police Department (BPD) officers arrested the man for assault with a dangerous weapon.</p>
<p>4 p.m.<br />
A student reported a suspicious man had been following her for several days. NUPD is investigating the matter.</p>
<p>4:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported his iPod missing from Snell Library, where he left it unattended.</p>
<p>5 p.m.<br />
An NUPD officer stopped three high school students outside Cahners Hall after he saw them smoking marijuana.</p>
<p>Friday, Oct. 22<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
Officers responded to a call from 118 Hemenway St. about water balloons being thrown off the roof. When they arrived, officers found five students and two non-students with wet clothes and water balloons. The students have been reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p><strong>Entry of the Week</strong><br />
2 a.m.<br />
Officers responded to a call from the Renaissance Parking Garage about a student who appeared to be assaulted. Upon arrival, the officers found a drunk 19-year-old student in one of the stairwells. NUPD officers are uncertain how the student became injured. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>5 p.m.<br />
Officers responded to a call from a student reporting someone broke into her apartment at 109 St. Stephen St. When officers arrived, they found someone attempted to break down the door.</p>
<p>6 pm.<br />
Officers broke up an argument between two students outside Davenport Commons B. Both students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Officers searched a student’s room in White Hall as part of an ongoing drug investigation. They found small amounts of marijuana. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>6:30 p.m.<br />
A student in Speare Hall reported she suspects her roommate has been stealing her gift cards and clothes from her. NUPD is investigating.</p>
<p>Saturday, Oct. 23<br />
1 a.m.<br />
Officers responded to a call about a loud party at 407 Huntington Ave. When officers arrived they found eight students, six of whom were underage. All of the students have been reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2:30 a.m.<br />
An officer saw Giorgio Parise and Michael Lehmann, both 19, fighting on Camden Street. Both students were arrested for disorderly conduct.</p>
<p>2 p.m.<br />
A student reported that her bicycle was stolen from outside Stetson East, where she left it Oct. 15.</p>
<p>11 p.m.<br />
Officers responded to a call about a loud party at Smith Hall. When officers arrived, they found five underaged students with alcohol. The students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Sunday, Oct. 24<br />
10 a.m.<br />
Officers responded to two separate calls about possible burglaries at 204 Hemenway St. Officers found no one in the apartments and were unsure if anything was missing. BPD is investigating the matter.</p>
<p>6 p.m.<br />
A students family reported a man on Huntington Avenue threatened them. NUPD has not yet found the man.</p>
<p>8 p.m.<br />
An officer saw two 13-year-old boys dragging a woman across Columbus Avenue. The officer chased and eventually caught the teens. The boys admitted they were trying to rob the woman who refused to give up her purse.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-69/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-68/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-68/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 07:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=12663</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Entry of the week: Sunday, Oct. 17, 4:15 p.m. An 18-year-old student on the sixth floor of International Village (INV) had his Facebook account hacked when he used another student’s laptop to check his profile but forgot to log out of it. The hacker changed the student’s birthday to Oct. 18, prompting many of his Facebook friends to wish him a happy birthday, even though his birthday isn’t until May. The investigation will continue to identify the culprit. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By John Jamieson, News Correspondent</p>
<p><strong>Entry of the week:</strong><br />
Sunday, Oct. 17<br />
4:15 p.m.<br />
An 18-year-old student on the sixth floor of International Village (INV)  had his Facebook account hacked when he used another student’s laptop  to check his profile but forgot to log out of it. The hacker changed the  student’s birthday to Oct. 18, prompting many of his Facebook friends  to wish him a happy birthday, even though his birthday isn’t until May.  The investigation will continue to identify the culprit.</p>
<p>Tuesday, Oct. 12<br />
1 p.m.<br />
A detective from the Northeastern University Division of Public Safety (NUPD) visited a 17-year-old Stetson East resident as part of an ongoing drug investigation. During the interview the detective confiscated five bags of marijuana totalling less than one ounce, 12 beers and a 60-ounce handle of vodka. The student will be reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR) and the investigation will continue.</p>
<p>1:15 p.m.<br />
The same NUPD detective visited a Stetson West dorm room to find an 18-year-old student whose name had come up in the previous investigation and found a 60-ounce handle of Jack Daniels. The bottle was confiscated and the student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:30 p.m.<br />
An NUPD detective smelled marijuana coming from a parked car in the Columbus Parking Garage. He questioned the car’s occupant, who had no affiliation with the university. The student said he was visiting his girlfriend, a student, and was in her car. The detective found and confiscated two illegal drugs from the car. David Ogara, 20, of Auburn, was arrested on charges of possession of Class B and Class E drugs, Soboxin and Oxycodone. The student returned during the incident, confirmed that Ogara had permission to be in her car, but denied having any knowledge of the drugs found.</p>
<p>8:15 p.m.<br />
Two West Village G residents called to report that their roommate verbally threatened them after a series of disagreements over cleanliness and other living matters. An NUPD officer contacted and interviewed the student and arrangements have been made through OSCCR to split up the roommates.</p>
<p>9:15 p.m.<br />
A White Hall resident called to report that her roommate verbally threatened her. They have been reported to OSCCR and arrangements have been made to separate the two.</p>
<p>Wednesday, Oct. 13<br />
11 p.m.<br />
A Resident Assistant (RA) in Kennedy Hall called to request assistance dealing with three students who appeared to be drinking. An NUPD officer investigated and confirmed this. The students, two 18-year-olds and a 19-year-old, have been reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Thursday, Oct. 14<br />
Noon<br />
A student reported her former boyfriend from high school, who she has a restraining order against, had been calling her. He lives in a town outside of Boston and NUPD officers are working with the towns government to ensure that precautions are put in place. Residence hall proctors were told not to allow him into her residence hall.</p>
<p>10 p.m.<br />
An NUPD detective went to White Hall as part of an ongoing drug investigation, but the student he was looking for was not there. Her roommate, 18, was present along with a guest unaffiliated with the university. The detective smelled marijuana and, after investigating, confiscated several grams totaling to less than one ounce as well as some hallucinogenic mushrooms. The guest claimed the drugs were his, though some were found in the roommate’s dresser. NUPD arrested a 17-year-old boy from Needham. The roommate was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Friday, Oct. 15<br />
1:15 a.m.<br />
NUPD officers responded to a call about an 18-year-old Boston University (BU) student who appeared intoxicated wandering aimlessly through Ruggles Station. It was determined that she was under the influence of alcohol, and was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center by ambulance. The Boston University Police Department was notified.</p>
<p>11:45 p.m.<br />
A student called to report an intoxicated 17-year-old student who came into her residence hall after drinking off-campus and vomited for 15 minutes. Emergency Medical Technicians (EMTs) determined the intoxicated student did not need to go to the hospital, but suggested that her floormates keep a close eye on her for the rest of the night. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Saturday, Oct. 16<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
An NUPD officer on patrol on the corner of Westland Avenue and Fenway saw two people holding up a third walking down the street. The officer questioned them and found all three had been drinking. Two were Berklee College of Music students, ages 18 and 20, and the third was a 17-year-old whom the officer believed to be a high school student. The 17-year-old was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center.</p>
<p>1 a.m.<br />
An RA reported detecting the odor of marijuana on the fifth floor of West Village F. After NUPD knocked, they heard students shuffling before opening the door. Officers saw multiple plastic cups, and confiscated rum and vodka from the refrigerator. The students, one 18-year-old and three 19-year-olds, were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1 a.m.<br />
An NUPD officer found a 19-year-old student unconscious lying in the grass between Cabot and Richards halls. EMTs assessed him and determined he did not need to be taken to the hospital. He was escorted back to his residence hall and will be reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:15 a.m.<br />
An NUPD officer found an 18-year-old student lying in the middle of Forsyth Street in a pool of her own vomit. Several passers-by who stopped to look told the officer that they saw her get out of a taxi, pay the driver and fall down in the road. She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center by ambulance and was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>3 a.m.<br />
An NUPD officer found a 23-year-old student with her head in her arms on a table in Cabot Court. Officers determined she was heavily intoxicated, but did not require hospitalization. Two officers walked her back to her apartment on Huntington Avenue. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>6 p.m.<br />
An NUPD officer saw a man aggressively panhandling for money from a woman in Ruggles Station. When the officer questioned the man, he learned the man was homeless and wanted for failure to appear in court for a trespassing offense in Boston. The officer arrested Brian Williams, 48, of Boston.</p>
<p>Sunday, Oct. 17<br />
12:15 a.m.<br />
A proctor in Speare Hall called to report that a man ran into the residence hall without showing any identification. Moments later, a student called to report a drunk person ran into his room and passed out on his roommates bed and vomited multiple times. Officers arrived, and woke up the man, a 19-year-old student who lives in an off-campus residence. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center. The officers called custodians to clean and disinfect the room.</p>
<p>12:45 a.m.<br />
An RA called to report a noisy group on the fourth floor of Bernstein Hall. An NUPD officer arrived and knocked on the door. After some scrambling, students opened the door and the officer saw plastic cups throughout the room and had guests leave. Empty beer was found around the room, in addition to a 30-pack of mostly unopened beers. The students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1 a.m.<br />
A caller reported seeing a disorderly group pass by the benches outside Kerr Hall and heard a windshield shatter immediately after. The group then went into Kennedy Hall. With the proctor’s help, NUPD officers were able to find and identify the members of the group. They were uncooperative and several lied when asked who came from where and who had just signed in. Others hid in bedrooms and closets. After interviewing students one-on-one, NUPD officers figured out which student they believe is most likely to have smashed the windshield. The 18-year-old Kennedy Hall resident was intoxicated. He was reported to OSCCR and will be summoned to court.</p>
<p>2:45 a.m.<br />
A 21-year-old student in Bernstein Hall called to report her 19-year-old roommate assaulted her while she was asleep in bed. NUPD officers came over, but the roommate had left. Once contacted, she returned to speak with the officer. She admitted to the assault and NUPD arrested Carly Scharf, 19, of New Jersey. While she was being booked, police found several fake IDs in her name. She was reported to OSCCR as well as the Massachusetts Registry of Motor Vehicles.</p>
<p><strong>Update: </strong>The charges against Scharf were dropped Nov. 18, 2010.</p>
<p>5 p.m.<br />
A 19-year-old student reported her laptop missing from Davenport A over the weekend. She left campus Friday and returned Sunday afternoon to find it missing. Two of her roommates were questioned, but they said they had no knowledge of the theft. The third roommate was unavailable. The investigation will continue.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-68/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-67/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-67/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 05:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=12537</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Friday, October 8, 11:30 p.m. The manager of Symphony Market reported a student urinated on the shelves in the rear of the store then made a purchase with his credit card. Officers were able to identify the student using the record of his credit card purchase. He has not been located yet.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>by Todd Feathers, News Correspondent</p>
<p>Monday, October 4<br />
4 p.m.<br />
A student reported her phone was stolen from a table in the Stetson East dining hall, where she left it unattended for five minutes.</p>
<p>10:30 p.m.<br />
A  student reported his bicycle stolen from outside Davenport A between 4  p.m. and 8 p.m. Two young men were seen stealing the bicycle on video  camera, but they have not been identified.</p>
<p>Tuesday, October 5<br />
9 a.m.<br />
Northeastern University Division of Public Safety (NUPD) officers searched the room of an 18-year-old student in Smith Hall as  part of an ongoing drug investigation. Small amounts of marijuana and  ecstasy were found. The student was reported to the Office of Student  Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>1:15 p.m.<br />
A  staff member in the Mugar Life Sciences Building reported a computer,  last seen a week earlier, missing from a lab on the fourth floor. The  spare key to the lab was also missing.</p>
<p>10 p.m.<br />
NUPD  officers responded to calls from Smith Hall about a fight between two  roommates over a pair of broken headphones. After interviewing the two  roommates, the officers arrested Alexander Sinyak, 19, for assault and  battery. Both roommates were relocated and Sinyak was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>10:30 p.m.<br />
NUPD  officers observed Christopher Bouldin, 23, standing outside Churchill  Hall. The officers knew Bouldin was not allowed on campus due to prior  trespassing violations, and he was arrested once again for trespassing.</p>
<p>Wednesday, October 6<br />
2 p.m.<br />
A  student returning to her apartment at 331 Huntington Ave. discovered  her door kicked in. When NUPD officers arrived, the apartment was empty  but had been burglarized. A laptop, iPod, jewelry and a wallet  containing a small amount of money were found to be missing.</p>
<p>6:15 p.m.<br />
A  student reported he suspected a friend stole his wallet to hold as  ransom for money the student owed him. When officers interviewed the  friend he admitted he took the wallet, but immediately took it to lost  and found. No money was missing from the wallet, and it was returned to  its owner. Both students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>8  p.m.<br />
A  student in West Village G told an RA his roommate frequently smoked  drugs in their room. The roommate admitted to smoking, but denied doing  it in the room. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>9:30 p.m.<br />
NUPD officers searched the room of an 18-year-old student in Smith Hall as  part of an ongoing drug investigation. They found a pipe, rolling  papers and grinder containing marijuana residue. The student was  reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Thursday, October 7<br />
1:40 a.m.<br />
Two  students reported they were approached outside the Massachusetts Avenue  T station by a drunk man who attempted to punch and kick them. Neither  was harmed.</p>
<p>9 a.m.<br />
NUPD  officers searched the room of an 18-year-old student in International  Village (INV) as part of an ongoing drug investigation. A variety of  marijuana paraphernalia was found. The student claimed the paraphernalia  belonged to a friend, but the friend denied ownership. Both students  were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>5:30 p.m.<br />
A  bookstore staff member reported a man trying to sell stolen books back  to the bookstore. Officers arrived and arrested Richard Parsons, 46, a  former Northeastern student who is now homeless. Parsons was also wanted  on outstanding warrants for identity fraud and larceny. He was taken to  Boston Medical Center to be treated for depression.</p>
<p>7:30 p.m.<br />
NUPD officers searched the room of an 18-year-old student in Stetson East as  part of an ongoing drug investigation. They found marijuana, a bong and  a large knife. The student and his roommate were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11 p.m.<br />
A 19-year-old student’s wallet was turned in to lost and found. The wallet contained two IDs, one of them fake. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Friday, October 8<br />
2 p.m.<br />
Two  men attempted to rob a student waiting for the elevator outside of West  Village E. The student screamed and ran away, and the suspects ran the  other direction. She was not harmed.</p>
<p>4:15 p.m.<br />
A student returning to her apartment at 108 Hemenway St. found her door kicked in. Two laptops, an iPod, a camera and a cell phone were stolen. NUPD officers believe the burglary may be related to the similar incident at 331 Huntington Ave. on Wednesday, October 6.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.<br />
The  manager of Symphony Market reported a student urinated on the shelves  in the rear of the store then made a purchase with his credit card.  Officers were able to identify the student using the record of his  credit card purchase. He has not been located yet.</p>
<p>Saturday, October 9<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
NUPD officers on Tremont Street saw two men carrying a drunk 18-year-old student. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>12:45 a.m.<br />
An  officer on Huntington Avenue saw a drunk 20-year-old student laying in  the grass near Speare Hall. EMTs evaluated her and allowed her to return  home with a friend. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:44 a.m.<br />
An  officer outside West Village F saw two men carrying a drunk 20-year-old  student. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and  reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2:30 a.m.<br />
A  student reported her wallet and cell phone were stolen from a table at  afterHOURS, where she left them unattended for five minutes.</p>
<p>2:45 a.m.<br />
NUPD  officers were called to INV where they found a drunk 18-year-old  student lying in the hallway. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess  Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>3 p.m.<br />
A student reported his bicycle stolen from Cabot Court between 4 p.m. Friday and 2:30 p.m. Saturday.</p>
<p>10:15 p.m.<br />
The  manager of Wollaston&#8217;s Market reported a student from the University of  Rhode Island was caught shoplifting. The student issued a trespassing  ban and will not be allowed on campus again.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.<br />
An RA in West Village C  reported a drunk student in the lobby. Officers arrived and found  Phillip Kerr, 22, who was wanted on an outstanding warrant for not  appearing in court. Kerr became combative and had to be restrained in  order to be taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center. When he was  released from the hospital, Kerr was arrested on the outstanding warrant  and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Sunday, October 10<br />
12:15 a.m.<br />
A proctor in Melvin Hall reported a student gave her ID to a friend in order to sign in guests. When officers arrived they found the student was drunk and had to be taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:30 a.m.<br />
A student in INV called NUPD to report her drunk 18-year-old friend needed medical attention. The friend was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>3:30 p.m.<br />
A  staff member in the Mugar Life Sciences Building reported a suspicious  man walking through the corridors checking doorknobs. When officers  arrived they found a 48-year-old man, with an arrest history of breaking  and entering, who claimed he was looking for a bathroom. Nothing was  stolen, so the man was released and issued a trespassing ban.</p>
<p>Monday, October 11<br />
6 p.m.<br />
A  student in Stetson East reported his roommate had two knives and  threatened to kill him during an argument. After interviewing both  roommates, officers arrested Yao-Ting Huang, 18, for assault with a  dangerous weapon. Both students were temporarily relocated, and Huang  has been reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>5:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported her bicycle stolen from outside Matthews Arena between 10 a.m. and 1:30 p.m.</p>
<p>Tuesday, October 12<br />
1 a.m.<br />
NUPD  officers were called to INV to investigate the smell of marijuana.  Officers discovered two 19-year-old students in a room with marijuana.  Neither student lives in the room, but one of the residents was found  and admitted he knew his friends were smoking in his room. All three  students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-67/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-66/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-66/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 07:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=12500</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Friday, Oct. 1 12:30 a.m. Friends of an 18-year-old student called to report he was intoxicated and vomiting heavily on the third floor of INV. When NUPD officers attempted to evaluate his condition, he offered them money to leave him alone. When they refused, he became combative and had to be restrained in the ambulance that brought him to Beth Israel Medical Center. He was reported to OSCCR. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By John Jamieson, News Correspondent</p>
<p>Monday, Sept. 27<br />
8:30 a.m.</p>
<p>A staff member from Hurtig Hall called to report several laptops stolen from a lab the previous night. There was no evidence of forced entry from the corridor, but there was a broken window in an inner door connecting two of the labs.</p>
<p>7 p.m.</p>
<p>An officer from the Northeastern University Division of Public Safety (NUPD) officer on patrol on The Fenway saw four students, ages 18 to 19, who appeared to be smoking marijuana behind the Back Bay Fens pump house. When questioned by the officer, one of the students claimed to not have smoked. All four will be reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>9:15 p.m.</p>
<p>A Resident Assistant (RA) in International Village (INV) reported the odor of marijuana coming from a dorm room. An NUPD officer found an 18-year-old student who was suspected of smoking. His bong was confiscated and will be reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>9:30 p.m.</p>
<p>The manager of the Wollaston&#8217;s in the Marino Center called to report two teens not affiliated with the university fleeing the store with a Gatorade and PowerBar without paying, following a brief confrontation with the manager. An NUPD officer who heard the radio call apprehended the suspects on Forsyth Street before they reached Ruggles Station. The manager came and identified the two, ages 15 and 16, and the police contacted their parents and arranged for relatives to pick them up. The two will be summoned to juvenile court.</p>
<p>Tuesday, Sept. 28<br />
11 a.m.</p>
<p>An 18-year-old student reported his backpack missing on Sept. 11. He left the bag in his room for a few hours with the door unlocked. His roommate had a few mutual friends over. When he returned the backpack was gone. Two weeks later the student reported it missing. The pack contained his passport, calculator and some personal papers.</p>
<p>9:30 p.m.</p>
<p>An RA reported the odor of marijuana coming from a room in West Village A. An NUPD officer investigated and found an 18-year-old student suspected of smoking. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Wednesday, Sept. 29<br />
3:30 p.m.</p>
<p>Two graduate students from Europe reported that late in the summer they were looking for an apartment on Craigslist.com. They found a suitable location near campus and wired several thousand dollars to a person in Spain as rent for the apartment. When the students arrived in the fall, they discovered there was no such address.</p>
<p>6 p.m.<br />
An NUPD officer saw three 18-year-old students smoking marijuana behind the Back Bay Fens pump house. They were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Thursday, Sept. 30<br />
9 p.m.</p>
<p>An NUPD officer patrolling Huntington Avenue saw a man give a 30-pack of beer to a second man. When the officer questioned the two, he found the first man was a 21-year-old Wentworth Institute of Technology student and the second was a 20-year-old Emerson College student. Both schools were notified, and the Wentworth student will be charged with purchasing alcohol for a minor. The beer was confiscated.</p>
<p>9:15 p.m.</p>
<p>An NUPD officer saw four students smoking marijuana behind the Back Bay Fens pump house. The students, three 18-year-olds and a 17-year-old, were all reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.<br />
An NUPD officer on patrol saw two students smoking marijuana while waiting at a bus stop on Tremont Street. Both students, ages 18 and 19, were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Friday, Oct. 1<br />
12:00 a.m.</p>
<p>A smoke detector went off in a sixth floor room in West Village F. When an NUPD officer arrived, he could smell smoke, but couldn&#8217;t see any in the hallway. He knocked on the door of the room, but there was no response. After hearing a cough from inside, the officer retrieved the master key from the Department of Housing and Residential Life and went in. The room was completely filled with smoke, so the officer pulled a fire alarm. There was a student unconscious on the couch, who was dragged by the officer to the hallway. There was also a small fire near the stove, which the officer put out with a fire extinguisher. On top of a lit burner, he found a pan whose bottom had been burned completely through. The officer also noticed evidence of drug use in the room. The student, 19, was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center, where it was determined that he was intoxicated. He was treated, released and reported to OSCCR. The incident is still under investigation.</p>
<p>12:30 a.m.</p>
<p>Friends of an 18-year-old student called to report he was intoxicated and vomiting heavily on the third floor of INV. When NUPD officers attempted to evaluate his condition, he offered them money to leave him alone. When they refused, he became combative and had to be restrained in the ambulance that brought him to Beth Israel Medical Center. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11:08 a.m.</p>
<p>Northeastern University Bookstore staff called to report a 21-year-old student who has repeatedly sold books to the store buyback after shoplifting them. An officer questioned her and the investigation will continue, but the NUPD said they anticipate filing criminal charges on behalf of Barnes &amp; Noble for the theft of more than $1,000 worth of books. She will also be reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2:30 p.m.</p>
<p>An NUPD detective returned to West Village F to question the student involved in the Oct. 1 kitchen fire about the evidence of drug use found. The student claimed not to be responsible for it, and his roommate admitted to the drug use. The detective confiscated a small amount of marijuana, drug paraphernalia and some pills of a medication that was not been prescribed to the student. The roommate provided the name of the student that gave him the pills to the NUPD.</p>
<p>4:30 p.m.</p>
<p>A student called to report her Westland Avenue apartment was repeatedly vandalized by objects thrown through the windows. The suspected perpetrators, also students, and NUPD and the Boston Police Department (BPD) are working together on this investigation.</p>
<p>5:30 p.m.</p>
<p>NUPD visited 110 St. Stephen St. as part of an ongoing investigation. When they arrived, they found two students, both age 19, in possession of beer and marijuana. They were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>6 p.m.</p>
<p>A 21-year-old student reported he lost his wallet somewhere near the restaurants on Huntington Avenue. His wallet contained $85 and several cards. He called to report his cards missing and discovered someone already tried to use his Husky Card at a dining hall.</p>
<p>6:15 p.m.</p>
<p>An NUPD officer visited 122 St. Stephen St. as part of an ongoing investigation. Upon arriving, the officer found and confiscated a small amount of marijuana and various drug paraphernalia. While the officer was still present, one resident returned to the room with $70 worth he had just purchased, which was also confiscated. The student admitted he frequently purchases marijuana, but doesn&#8217;t sell, and occasionally shares with his friends. Because of this sharing, the student may be charged for illegal distribution. All three students, age 19, have been reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>6:30 p.m.</p>
<p>NUPD officers saw five students, 18, behind the Back Bay Fens pump house. An odor of marijuana was present, but there was not visual proof of the students smoking. All five were reported to OSCCR for suspicion of smoking.</p>
<p>Saturday, Oct. 2<br />
12:15 a.m.</p>
<p>A student called to request help for her friend, 18, who was in the lobby of White Hall too intoxicated to stand. She was drinking that night in Kerr Hall. She was taken by ambulance to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and will be reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1 a.m.</p>
<p>A student called to report an 18-year-old student was severely intoxicated in Speare Place. She had been drinking at an off-campus party. She was taken to Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital for treatment, as Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center was full. She was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2 a.m.</p>
<p>An NUPD officer on patrol saw two males holding up a 23-year-old female student who was unable to walk by herself. She had been drinking at an off-campus party, and was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center by ambulance.</p>
<p>5:30 p.m.</p>
<p>An NUPD officer saw two students sharing a marijuana blunt behind the Back Bay Fens pump house. For one of them, it was his third marijuana offense in two years. Both were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>10 p.m.</p>
<p>An 18-year-old student called to report she was receiving threatening and harassing phone calls from someone. She suspected it was either her former boyfriend, who is attending college in Arkansas, or his 14-year-old brother. NUPD contacted her former boyfriend, who denied making the calls and agreed it could be his younger brother. He called the brother, who admitted to making the calls, demanded he stop harassing the former girlfriend, and apologized on his younger brother&#8217;s behalf for the behavior.</p>
<p>Sunday, Oct. 3<br />
1 a.m.</p>
<p>A caller reported an 18-year-old student was exhibiting signs of intoxication and being under the influence of drugs in Smith Hall. NUPD found he had been drinking off-campus and had taken ecstasy. The student was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and was reported to OSCCR. He also provided information to NUPD about where he got the ecstasy.</p>
<p>1:30 a.m.</p>
<p>A caller reported an 18-year-old student vomiting in White Hall. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center by ambulance and was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2 a.m.</p>
<p>A 19-year-old student called to request assistance for another 19-year-old student who was intoxicated at 650 Columbus Ave. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Monday, Oct. 4</p>
<p>2 a.m.<br />
An RA reported the odor of marijuana coming from the fourth floor of INV. NUPD officers investigated and found an intoxicated 18-year-old student. They confiscated a small amount of marijuana and a nearly-full large bottle of tequila. The student was reported to OSCCR.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/10/crime-log-66/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Log</title>
		<link>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/09/crime-log-65/</link>
		<comments>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/09/crime-log-65/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 06:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>The Huntington News</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime Log]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://huntnewsnu.com/?p=12350</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Sunday, September 26, 8 p.m. Officers outside INV saw an intoxicated 21-year-old man fall. He was accompanied by an intoxicated 18-year-old student who refused to cooperate with officers. The student was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>by Todd Feathers, News Correspondent</p>
<p><strong>Crime Log entry of the week:</strong> Saturday, September 25</p>
<p>11:45 p.m.<br />
NUPD officers were called to Smith Hall, where a 23-year-old intoxicated  woman had entered the residence hall without signing in. She was unable  to tell officers her name or the name of the student she was visiting.  She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center.</p>
<p>Monday, September 20<br />
10 a.m.<br />
A student reported his jacket stolen from a bathroom in Behrakis Health Sciences Center between 10 a.m. and 2 p.m. on Sept. 16.</p>
<p>8 p.m.<br />
A student reported his bicycle was stolen from a fence on Symphony Road between 6:30 p.m. and 8 p.m.</p>
<p>9 p.m.<br />
A student reported his bicycle was stolen from outside the Marino Recreation Center between noon and 8 p.m.</p>
<p>9:45 p.m.<br />
A student walking on Forsyth Street reported three teenagers stole his laptop and then ran away. NUPD officers are working with the Boston Transit Police to find the thieves.</p>
<p>Tuesday, September 21<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
A caller reported an argument in White Hall. When officers arrived, they discovered Shannon Murphy, 18, got into a fight with her 18-year-old non-student friend she knew from high school, who had a restraining order against Murphy. She was arrested for assault and battery and violating a restraing order and reported to the Office of Student Conduct and Conflict Resolution (OSCCR).</p>
<p>6:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported her wallet, which contained $5, was stolen from outside a raquet ball court in Cabot Physical Recreation Center between 3 p.m. and 5 p.m.</p>
<p>7:30 p.m.<br />
A teenager stole an iPhone from the wife of a faculty member inside Dana Research Center. The suspect got away.</p>
<p>Wednesday, September 22<br />
2 p.m.<br />
A staff member reported her wallet, which contained $10, was stolen from her purse in the Egan Engineering Science Research Center between noon and 2 p.m.</p>
<p>8:15 p.m.<br />
The NUPD was notified that a smoke detector was tampered with in a West Village E apartment. When officers arrived they found two students and a marijuana pipe in the room. The NUPD believe that the smoke alarm was disabled by friends of the students, whom the pipe may belong to. They have all been reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>9:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported his wallet, which contained $20, was stolen from an ATM in the Marino Center, where he left it.</p>
<p>Thursday, September 23<br />
3 p.m.<br />
A student reported his bicycle was stolen from outside West Village E between Friday, Sept. 17 and Wednesday, Sept. 22.</p>
<p>10:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported she lost her wallet on Huntington Avenue. Her credit cards were used off campus before she could cancel them.</p>
<p>Friday, September 24<br />
1:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported his laptop was stolen from a sidewalk on St. Cyprian Avenue.</p>
<p>1:30 p.m.<br />
A student reported the rear wheel of his bicycle was stolen from Centennial Common between 6 a.m. and 1 p.m.</p>
<p>11:30 p.m.<br />
A student in Speare Hall reported her 18-year-old roommate was intoxicated and vomiting. The roommate was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center. She will be reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Saturday, September 25<br />
12:30 a.m.<br />
A proctor at 337 Huntington Ave. reported that a student who appeared drunk signed in and went upstairs. A Resident Assistant (RA) found a 19-year-old student intoxicated and passed out in his room and called the NUPD. The student was evaluated by EMTs and found to be OK. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:15 a.m.<br />
A student found vomit on the floor of her St. Stephen Street apartment, and her roommate locked in the bathroom. When officers arrived they found the 19-year-old roommate heavily intoxicated. She was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>1:30 a.m.<br />
An RA in Smith Hall reported an 18-year-old student vomiting in a bathroom. He was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>10 a.m.<br />
A student reported possible identity theft after discovering someone hacked into her Facebook account and downloaded pictures of her personal documents.</p>
<p>8 p.m.<br />
A NUPD officer saw a 21-year-old student hand two cases of beer to two 18-year-old students. They were all reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>10:30 p.m.<br />
A caller reported a drunk 17-year-old student stumbling down Hemenway Street. The student was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>11 p.m.<br />
NUPD received notice that someone had violated the roof door alarm of 110 St. Stephen St. When officers arrived they found three 19-year-old students sitting on the roof with marijuana. The students were reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>Sunday, September 26<br />
12:35 a.m.<br />
A student told officers she was assaulted by another student as she was leaving a party on Symphony Road. She was later able to identify Anthony Bitetto, 20, as the perpetrator. He was arrested for indecent assault and battery and reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>2:30 a.m.<br />
An RA in Speare Hall reported seeing a student asleep on a couch in the lobby. The student was drinking the night before and received a black eye in a fight. He was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>3 a.m.<br />
A student reported his 22-year-old non-student friend was unconscious in his apartment at 118 Hemenway St. The friend was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center.</p>
<p>3:35 a.m.<br />
NUPD officers were called to International Village (INV) where a student reported a man writing with a marker on the wall. Officers arrested Alec Selinger, 18, for wanton destruction of private property, and was reported to OSCCR.</p>
<p>8 p.m.<br />
Officers outside INV saw an intoxicated 21-year-old man fall. He was accompanied by an intoxicated 18-year-old student who refused to cooperate with officers. The student was taken to Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and reported to OSCCR.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://huntnewsnu.com/2010/09/crime-log-65/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
